hornyonlinematch.com 2011-10-07

# Horny Online Match - PRIVACY POLICY

This website is owned and operated by Amorix Ltd (Company Number 4473833) trading as White Label Dating. Our privacy policy relates only to information that we obtain from you and not to information obtained by third parties or via linked websites.

**What information will be collected?**

The type of information we will collect about you includes: 

  1. your name, address, occupation, phone number and e-mail address 
  2. the information included in your membership profile and that you provide via our client surveys, your interests and details about the services you specifically request.

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit written consent. 

**How will the information be used?**

The information you provide to us when using this website will be used to administer your user account with us (including notifying you of any updates or services, should you consent to this), customise the site according to your interests, ensure that you are complying with the terms and conditions of use and to comply with our statutory and regulatory obligations. By registering a profile you consent to the wider dissemination of the information you provide in that profile to the other users of the site, some of whom may be outside the USA to achieve your joint objectives. We will keep your personal information confidential except where you have posted it for publication or display, to the extent that we are compelled to disclose it by law or to comply with an instruction of a regulatory body of competent jurisdiction. We adhere to strict security procedures and your personal information will be held securely to ensure no unauthorised disclosure or access. 

By checking the appropriate box on the new account registration form you consent to receive compatible matches, tips, announcements and special offers from Amorix ltd Whitelabel platform and selected partners from address support@alcuda.com to the e-mail address which you have provided. Should you wish to unsubscribe or reduce the number of e-mails you receive from us you can alter your preferences by visiting the ['My Account'](http://hornyonlinematch.com/mypage.php) section of this website and select the emails you dont want to receive by ticking the corresponding checkboxes. Also you can unsubscribe from a specific email by using the unsubscribe link from the email you don't want to receive any longer. 

**Your Rights**

Should you wish to obtain a copy of the personal data that we hold on you, please send an e-mail to datarequest@alcuda.com . If you believe that the information we hold about you is inaccurate or if you wish us to cease processing your data for any particular purpose or purposes, write to us at the above address or e-mail datarequest@alcuda.com . If you have a complaint regarding any breach of this privacy policy, contact us at support@alcuda.com 

**Tracking**

When visiting our web pages, we generally use tracking technologies which record information about you automatically. This information does not identify you personally and is used to ensure that our Web pages stay compatible with a selection of browsers and systems. 

Please click [here](http://hornyonlinematch.com/helptandc.asp?s=s) to access our full privacy policy.
